Hi guys, welcome to my YouTube vlog.  For
today's video, it's simple.
We will be reviewing the Flex 1D 41,100.
So, what are we waiting for?  Let's go.
So, for product description, it is
infrared ceramic cooker, suitable for
any pot.  10 power level settings, 10
temperature level settings, 50 to 500
celsus high efficiency
uh high energy high efficiency up to 3
hours timer, touch sensitive panel, lock
child feature and then up to 10 kg so
he got the most out of that heavy duty of 10
kg.  So at least he can carry 10 L
of liquid.
Then up to 2,000 watts and then 1
year of electricity.  1 year
warranty for the price of Php3,298.
So you can buy him in any part of
Avenson.  So let's write it out.  So
his plug is just flat.  So
he has no problem in the Philippines and
then his power is just up and down.  So let's
start with the lowest.
That's it.  Then he functions timer, lock and
then on, off and temperatures.  Hot
surface.  So when you say hot surface,
this is the one that glows red.  So just be
careful.
Cook on top surface as hot after.  Please do
n't touch.  So his maximum hot spot is only 26 cm
because he's small.
That's it.
Once it starts, he's already stabbed.
So you will interface automatically.  So
you're going to turn this function
on.  So once it's on, going to put the
function.  That's it.  This is the power.
So you have weak power.  There you go.  Because
you want to change the temperature.  You
put the temperature there.  And the
highest is 500 which is very hot
.  So if you want it to reach
500, it will change color
until it reaches 500. So you can see
the cooking pot there, or the heater itself.
That's how you can see him in
black and white.  So I only use
100.
So that's already 100.  Just to
figure it out.
Right now, I'm using only teplon.
This one to try on.  So, using 500
only using 100 temperature doesn't
heat up of course.
So let's try until 250
so that its heat can escape.
This is 250.  His color has changed a bit
.  Okay.  So until
his temperature.  Look at this.
That's it.  He won't boil yet.  That means
the power of the temperature is only that hot
.  So that's an estimate.  Oh, that's it.
He's not hot yet.
So there you go.  It's waterproof.
So no problem.
So let's strengthen the
function of his power if you don't know.
I prefer only 16.
There you go, hot surface.  How is he?
He is full.  Tell me,
it's hot overall.  Even though the line is
still hot.  There he is.
He's about to roll over.  So you can
see that he's hot.
So you can see that he's eating even though
you didn't use it.  using the
temperature 500. There it is.
He's so charming.  So that's all I have,
but it's still the same.  It's very nice.  That's just
how he is when you put him down.  That's
it.
So you can lock it for
children, just like a child protection hot
surface.  He is very well.  It's so
easy to use.  So using the knob only to
control the power.   It's very
basic.  So anyone can
use it.
So I turned him off.  I just turned
him off.  He will automatically die.  There you go.
So just be careful.  That's a hard hot
surface.  Okay.  It's boiling.
So I didn't cook anymore.  So
he's at least stuck.  There,
he's still on a hot surface until
he cools down.  So you can hear the noise.  That means
he's still using electricity.  So
the best way is to turn him off.  That's it.  But
be careful because it's hot.  Well, the
good thing about it is that it's easy to
clean.  So even though I didn't
use him, that's how I didn't
use him.  I just need
water for him.
It has an easy-to-clean surface.  That's
just a tissue.  But of course that depends on how
you cook.  There you go.  But the best way is to
cool it down for me first, is that
okay? So if you do like
this kind of product review, please
do like and subscribe to my YouTube channel.
Thank you very much for the peace out.